steelmasterusa.com 2014-02-09

# SteelMaster - View Our Privacy Policy | SteelMaster USA

## Privacy Policy

##  SteelMaster Buildings Email Privacy Policy

We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information

* * *

**Why did you receive an email from us?**

If you received a mailing from us, you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.

* * *

**How we protect your privacy**

We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.

* * *

**Sharing and Usage**

We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.

* * *

**How can you stop receiving email from us?**

Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email. If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to [marketing@steelmasterusa.com](mailto:marketing@steelmasterusa.com) for review.

### SteelMaster hangar lets Minnesota pilot soar

Mark Hobson is an aviation enthusiast who has flown various types of aircraft and has his pilot’s license. But when the time came for Mark to purchase his first airplane, he decided it would be best…

### SteelMaster survives Snowmageddon

Above: A snow angel made by a SteelMaster employee. Winter storm Leon swept through the southeastern United States on Tuesday, creating unthinkable traffic jams and forcing some children to sleep in their…

### SteelMaster wins Roaring 20 for third consecutive year

SteelMaster Buildings is proud to announce it has received Inside Business’s Roaring 20 award for the third year in a row. The award recognizes the 20 fastest growing businesses in Hampton Roads.…
